matchmyrx.com 2019-04-13

# MatchMyRx: Personal Medication Record

## Privacy Policy

## Last Update: 01/09/2017

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the MatchMyRx web application (the “App”) and related website located at www.matchmyrx.com (including the mobile-optimized versions of such website, the “Site”) owned by PRX CONTROL SOLUTIONS, LLC (“we” or “us”). The App and the Site are referred to together as the “Application”. ‘You’ refers to any user of the Application, including individuals who use the Application to understand their medications, healthcare providers who use the Application to provide better prescription data to patients and med students who use the Application to learn about prescription patterns and practices. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, including with respect to (a) the collection and processing of Health Information (as defined below), (b) the collection and processing of your geo-location data (c) our cookies policy and (d) marketing, please do not click “MATCH MY RX” or “GET RECORD “and do not use the Application.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

MatchMyRx respects your right to privacy. MatchMyRx does not collect any personal information from those who visit the site.

We only collect information through the online form, the use of cookies, web beacons and navigational data collection. While we cannot directly identify you, in some jurisdictions, this information is still subject to applicable data protection laws and requires your consent to our cookies policy as described below.

## Collecting and Using Your Information

Whenever you submit information via our App or Site, or otherwise in connection with your use of the Application, including, but not limited to, by telephone or email with customer service, you consent to the collection and processing of your Health Information and geo-location data and other personal information you provide to us, our cookies policy, cross-border transfer of data, and the use of your data for marketing purposes, all in accordance with this Privacy Policy. MatchMyRx respects your right to privacy.

During the use of the the Application you will input other Information such as your age, gender, your conditions and the medications you take.

You may also send your healthcare provider your “Record”, which includes the results of the match between medications and conditions. Sharing of your “Record in this manner is solely your responsibility.

## Automatic Data Collection

We collect information about your use of the Site (IP address, type of computing or mobile device you use, language of your operating system, the Internet browser you are using, geo-location and use of the Site) through the use of various technologies, such as cookies, web beacons and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, clickstream). For more information on our cookies policy, please see below.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a visitor’s browser. The browser provides this piece of text to the device of the originating visitor when this visitor returns. We use cookies to help personalize your MatchMyRx experience. A “persistent” cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but allow you to modify security settings so that you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis or reject all cookies. You can configure your web browser to remove cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” section.

Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. If you delete or disable cookies from our Site, some parts or functions of the Site may not work properly for you.

## HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions, comments, requests, or concerns related to this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices for our Application, please contact us at:

PRX Control Solutions, LLC

1010 NE, 2nd Ave, Miami, FL 33131

## CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

From time to time we may need to change this Privacy Policy. You will be informed of such change in advance, and you will always have the possibility to stop using the service as explained above.

#### Get in touch

####  __ info@prxcontrolsolutions.com
